If your goal is to make $1 million a year, you need systems, open up notion, and create
a company wiki with the following areas.
Sales, video, hiring, people, design, finance, product, creative, marketing, operations,
technology, copywriting, interviewing, monetization, audience growth, customer success, community
building.
The stronger your systems, the stronger your business.
This might seem overwhelming at first, and that's completely normal.
The good news is, I'm here to show you the exact playbook and blueprint you can implement
immediately.
The ability to achieve your goals will be measured by your ability to implement bulletproof
systems in your company.
Each system is the building block to your compounding success.